

## **Profile**

Dynamic QC Associate knowledgeable in **Web Development** and scripting languages. Looking to integrate several years of a unique skill set as a scientist into a tech career. Highly motivated with strong problem solving skills and a passion for coding.

www.tepeupotter.com | www.linkedin.com/in/tepeu-potter

## **Projects**

#### Stock Market Social Media App, www.portfoliorater.com

JUNE 2020 - PRESENT

- Social media website to share, like, comment and view stock market portfolios visualized with Chart.js
- Written in React , Node.js, and Express using MongoDB and Firebase for the back-end
- Sass was used for component styling and Redux for state management and Finnhub for the API
- Fully fleshed out application with real concurrent users.

#### Pixelated Exercise Tracker, www.pixelatedyear.com

JANUARY 2021 - PRESENT

- Visual calendar to track workout frequency and intensity throughout the year
- React application which makes use of CSS Grid and React Hooks
- Login with third part applications such as Google and Github, or preview anonymously
- Uses Next.js framework and Firebase for the backend

#### Shopify Applications, tzpdevstore.myshopify.com

JANUARY 2021 - PRESENT

- Voice command navigation and banner popup applications for Shopify merchant stores
- Written with React using Next.js framework. Uses Shopify's API, Polaris component library, and Apollo GraphQL
- Vanilla javascript used to embed client side javascript and CSS with script tags that employ jQuery

#### Crypto Currency Ranking, www.yourcryptorank.com

MAY 2021 - PRESENT

- Vote on your favorite cryptocurrencies to submit to Global Rankings. Drag and drop to sort your rankings.
- Uses coingecko's API and the Borda Count method for vote tallying.
- Global Rankings page also serves as links to coingecko for more coin specific information.

#### Portfolio Website, www.tepeupotter.com

MAY 2021 - JUNE 2021

- Made using React and Next.js with a minimalist design
- Focuses on building reusable components

#### **Details**

Austin, TX 4105624890 <u>tepeupotter@gmail.com</u>

#### Skills

JavaScript ES6

React / Redux

CSS / Sass

MongoDb

**Firebase** 

**Shopify Liquid** 

Express / Koa

Visual Basic for Applications

Adobe Photoshop

Github

## Languages

English

Spanish

# **Employment History**

## Quality Control Assocaite, Luminex Corporation, Austin, TX

AUGUST 2019 - PRESENT

- Realized extreme redundancies in data report generation and went above and beyond to teach myself Microsoft's event driven programming language Visual Basic in order to code macros to automate the process. Calculated potential savings of over 500 hours a year
- Additional scripts for data extraction used for CAPA plans and to determine monthly KPIs
- Selected as one of two associates to collaborate with R&D to perform stability and validation testing for our COVID serology assays

### Scientific Associate, Worldwide Clinical Trials, Austin, TX

JANUARY 2018 - AUGUST 2019

- Managed multiple clinical studies simultaneously, requiring flexibility and time-management to meet tight deadlines and shifting priorities
- Selected as one of two analysts to be cross trained into newly expanded pharmacogenomics department. Performed genetic testing to screen for clinical trial recruitment

# **Education**

Bachelor of Science, Florida State University, Tallahassee, FL

AUGUST 2011 - MAY 2016

• BrightFutures FAS Scholar